## MIRA BARRIENTOS

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

O Colombia, Medellin, 050022

+573505325406

josemb125@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

• BACHELOR UNIVERSIDAD EAFIT, 2020 Software Engineering

#### LINKS

- GitHub: https://github.com/josewweee
- LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-maria-mira-b-6699a5212">https://www.linkedin.com/in/jose-maria-mira-b-6699a5212</a>

## SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- NextJs
- Tailwind
- React
- React Native
- lonic
- Angular
- Firebase
- CSS
- Tailwind
- Unity
- Python
- C#
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

### LANGUAGES

- English
- Spanish

#### ABOUT ME

Developer with a background in web, mobile and game development, having 3+ years of practice and leadership building interactive experiences. Disciplined, organized, humble and righteous person. Committed to good morals, continuous learning, innovation and development of optimal solutions.

Great enthusiastic teamwork, considered helpful, creative, assertive and cautious.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER | JULY 2020 - PRESENT talos digital, remote

- Created big web projects with brand new technologies at the moment ( NextJs and Tailwind ), manage to learn on the go, synchronize with a fully remote team, deliver quality products and made several on-boarding process to new developers.
- Mentored team members in development, issues and technical progression.
- Optimized web pages to increase performance by a 100%, and SEO by a 70%, using coding best practices and good approaches to bottlenecks.
- Created custom video player, audio recognition softwares and data collectors platforms that worked as the core of new platforms.

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AND CEO | JANUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2019 barbero express app, medellín

- Developed, launched and managed the commercialization of a successful app along with other 2 engineer using scrum, Firebase, Angular and Ionic.
- Collaborated with other developers to identify and alleviate software errors and inefficiencies.
- Discussed project progress with customers, collected feedback on different stages and directly addressed concerns.
- $\cdot$  Got over 1,000 downloads, more than 200 users online at the same time and more than 3,000 usd in revenues.

# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | FEBRUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2017 independent, freelancer, medellín

- Created eye catching and functional digital desing concepts across varius platforms to strengthen company brand and identity
- Tested websited and performed troubleshooting prior deployment.